moserbaerhomevideo.com 2011-03-01

# Buy Devotional Films | Rare Classic Movies Online | Buy Hindi TV Serials | Online Movie Store for All

We, namely **Moser Baer Entertainment Limited (MBEL)** respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy provides the manner your data is collected and used by MBEL. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing this web site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Further by accepting the Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

  **INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU :  
**When you use our Site, we collect and store your personal information from you viz: name including first and last name, e-mail address, mobile phone number and contact details, ZIP/Postal code, demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address and durables owned); preferences and interests (such as news, sports, travel and so on); financial information (like account or credit card numbers); and opinions of features on our websites.

  We automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from :  
\- web server cookie stored on your hard drive  
\- an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use  
\- the domain server through which you access our service  
\- the type of computer you are using  
\- the type of web browser you are using  
\- the pages you visit/access  
\- the links you click on our site  
\- the number of times you access the page.

  **WHO COLLECTS THE INFORMATION ?  
**We collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit our site.

  We collect the personally identifiable information from you when you register with us on our Website to avail of any of our service or product available on such site, whether for any contest or otherwise. During registration for any contest you are required to give us your contact information (such as name, email address, date of birth, gender, address, pin code, cell number, occupation and interests). Upon registration users may receive communications from MBEL (e.g. newsletters, updates)

  We may use this information to contact you about the services you are using on our site and services in which you have expressed interest. We will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process, on-line survey, or contest or any combination thereof. The Site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites which we do not own, manage or control.

  **HOW IS THE INFORMATION USED?  
**We may use your email address to send you reminder and registration confirmation, Special offers, News letters, Changes in the service's policy or terms of use and event based communications such as order information, renewal notices, invites, reminders etc.

  We may use your personal information to:  
\- help us provide you with the desired Services and products from our Website;  
\- tailor our sites to your interest  
\- Provide personalized features  
\- to get in touch with you in the case of policy changes

  We use contact information internally to :  
\- direct our efforts for product improvement  
\- contact you as a survey respondent  
\- notify you if you win any contest; and  
\- send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers

  Generally, we use anonymous traffic information to:  
\- remind us of who you are in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service from both an advertising and an editorial perspective;  
\- help diagnose problems with our server  
\- administer our Web sites  
\- track your session so that we can understand better how people use our sites

  We shall transfer information about you if MBEL is acquired by or merged with another company.

  **WITH WHOM WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED?  
**We limit access to personal information about you to employees and Affiliates (described as MBEL's licensors, MBEL's content providers and MBEL authorised content distributors) who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

  We do not rent, sell or share your personal information and we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information unless: 

  * to provide products or services you've requested
  * we have your permission
  * to help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person, violations of MBEL terms of use or to defend against legal claims;
  * Special circumstances such as compliance with court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure.
  * We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable and email address information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information and email address submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information and email address, we cannot guarantee its absolute security, including by way of phishing indulged in by other parties.

  **POLICY UPDATES  
**We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site.

  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

  If we decide to make changes in our email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we decide to change our email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
